Yellowstone National Park
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Yellowstone National Park
2.1.1.1.31
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1251
- Yellowstone National Park, 2.1.1.1.31
  - Yellowstone Station, Oregon Short Line, 1911; 32; 16000; 6; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Yellowstone Station, 1911; 33; 16001; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Wylie Camp, 1911; 34; 16002; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Wylie Camp near western entrance, 1911; 35; 16003; 84; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Christmas tree park, 1911; 36; 16004; 80; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Cascades of the Firehole River, 1911; 37; 16005; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Firehole Cascade, 1911; 38; 16006; 88; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - On the Madison River, 1911; 39; 16007; 56; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - The Madison River, 1911; 40; 16008; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Fountain Hotel and Lower Basin, 1911; 41; 16009; 7; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Fountain Hotel, 1911; 42; 16010; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Lower Geyser Basin, Taft Geyser, 1911; 43; 16011; 23; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Lower Basin near Fountain Hotel, 1911; 44; 16012; 8; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Lower Geyser Basin, 1911; 45; 16013; 102; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Lower Geyser Basin, Paint Pots, 1911; 46; 16014; 18; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Lower Basin Paint Pots, close view, 1911; 47; 16015; 37; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Lower Basin Paint Pots, 1911; 48; 16016; 98; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Pool near Paint Pots, Lower Basin, 1911; 49; 16017; 103; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Crater of the Great Fountain Geyser, 1911; 50; 16018; 78; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Excelsior basin overflow into Firehole River, 1911; 51; 16019; 79; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Irvin Buttes and outlet from Excelsior basin, 1911; 52; 16020; 104; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Excelsior Geyser basin, 1911; 53; 16021; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  - Pool near Prismatic Lake, Excelsior basin, 1911; 54; 16022; 106; 5x7 (Box 1251)
  Box 1252
- Yellowstone National Park, 2.1.1.1.31
  - Pool near Prismatic Lake to show color, Excelsior Geyser basin, 1911; 1; 16023; 73; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Pool near Prismatic Lake to show color, Excelsior basin, 1911; 2; 16024; 63; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Prismatic Lake stream showing colors, Excelsior basin, 1911; 3; 16025; 64; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Prismatic Lake and Excelsior Geyser, 1911; 4; 16027; 60; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Upper Geyser Basin from distance, 1911; 5; 16028; 107; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Upper Geyser Basin looking toward Giantess, 1911; 6; 16029; 34; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - The White Dome near Lower Basin, 1911; 7; 16031; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Old Faithful Inn, general view, 1911; 8; 16032; 39; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Old Faithful Inn, side front, 1911; 9; 16033; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Porch of Old Faithful Inn, 1911; 10; 16034; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Old Faithful in action, 1911; 11; 16035; 46; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Old Faithful from formation near Giantess, Upper Basin, 1911; 12; 16036; 108; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Old Faithful in eruption, 1911; 13; 16037; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Old Faithful Inn and Bee Hive Geyser, 1911; 14; 16038; 33; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Sponge Geyser, Upper Basin, 1911; 15; 16039; 96; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Bee Hive cone, looking toward Old Faithful Inn, Upper Basin, 1911; 16; 16040; 82; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Lion, Lioness and Cub Geysers, Upper Basin, 1911; 17; 16041; 62; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - The Giantess playing, 1911; 18; 16042; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Party at the Thumb, 1911; 19; 16043; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Kepler Cascades, 1911; 20; 16044; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Kepler Cascade, looking downstream, 1911; 21; 16045; 14; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Road to Yellowstone Lake, 1911; 22; 16046; 54; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Yellowstone Lake and road, 1911; 23; 16047; 38; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Road to Lake Hotel, 1911; 24; 16048; 119; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Yellowstone Lake, trees in foreground, 1911; 25; 16050; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Yellowstone Lake through trees, taken near hotel, 1911; 26; 16051; 115; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Lake Hotel, 1911; 27; 16052; 53; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Lower Falls from Lookout Point, 1911; 28; 16055; 146; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Lower Falls from Grandview Point, 1911; 29; 16056; 13; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Great Falls from edge of canyon, 1911; 30; 16058; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Great Falls, taken from Red Rock, 1911; 31; 16059; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Canyon from Red Rock, looking away from falls, 1911; 32; 16060; 145; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Canyon from Inspiration Point, looking away from falls, 1911; 33; 16061; 149; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Yellowstone Grand Canyon looking toward Great Falls, 1911; 34; 16063; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Grand Canyon from Artist’s Point looking toward Great Falls, 1911; 35; 16064; 94; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Grand Canyon of the Yellowstone from Artist’s Point, looking away from falls, 1911; 36; 16065; 77; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Turret effect before reaching Inspiration Point, canyon, 1911; 37; 16066; 151; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Color effect of turrets, Inspiration Point, Grand Canyon of Yellowstone, 1911; 38; 16067; 141; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Taken from Grandview Point with eagle’s nest, Grand Canyon, 1911; 39; 16069; 140; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Rock formation in canyon, 1911; 40; 16070; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Yellowstone Grand Canyon, showing peculiar rock formation, 1911; 41; 16071; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Roaring Mountain between Norris and Mammoth, 1911; 42; 16072; 40; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Norris Geyser Basin, 1911; 43; 16073; 45; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Constant Geyser, Norris Basin, 1911; 44; 16074; 31; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Beautiful pool near Norris Geyser Basin, 1911; 45; 16075; 20; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Emerald Pool at Norris Basin, 1911; 46; 16076; 28; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Rustic Falls near Golden Gate, 1911; 47; 16077; 29; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Golden Gate and Bunsen Peak, 1911; 48; 16078; 16; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Golden Gate looking north, 1911; 49; 16079; 44; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - Golden Gate looking south, 1911; 50; 16080; 47; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - The Hoodoos near Silver Gate, 1911; 51; 16081; 247; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  - The Hoodoos, 1911; 52; 16082; 5x7 (Box 1252)
  Box 1253
- Yellowstone National Park, 2.1.1.1.31
  - Mammoth Hot Spring Hotel and Fort Yellowstone, 1911; 1; 16083; 117; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Mammoth Hotel and Fort Yellowstone, 1911; 2; 16084; 113; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Pulpit Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 3; 16085; 89; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - General view of Jupiter Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 4; 16086; 97; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Pulpit Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 5; 16087; 99; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Minerva Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 6; 16088; 109; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 7; 16089; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Hymen Terrace, general view and Devil’s Thumb, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 8; 16090; 125; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Looking down on Hymen Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 9; 16091; 112; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Hymen Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 10; 16092; 105; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Cleopatra Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 11; 16093; 101; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Looking down on Cleopatra Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 12; 16094; 11; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Cleopatra Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 13; 16095; 22; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Cleopatra Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 14; 16096; 26; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Cleopatra Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 15; 16097; 86; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Cupid’s Cave, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 16; 16098; 118; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Cupid’s Cave, general view, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 17; 16099; 129; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Mound Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 18; 16100; 76; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Orange Geyser at Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 19; 16101; 100; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Deer on edge of forest, 1911; 20; 16102; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Lodge pole pine forest, 1911; 21; 16103; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Mistletoe on tree, 1911; 22; 16105; 142; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Shooting star [plant], 1911; 23; 16106; 274; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Larkspur, 1911; 24; 16107; 280; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Wild phlox, 1911; 25; 16108; 281; 5x7 (Box 1253)
  - Bear at Norris, 1911; 26; 16110; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Woodchuck on the edge of the lake, 1911; 27; 16111; 249; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Deer in woods, 1911; 28; 16112; 201; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Bear at Norris, 1911; 29; 16113; 153; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Black bear, 1911; 30; 16114; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Deer, close-up, 1911; 31; 16115; 188; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Deer in the trees, 1911; 32; 16116; 187; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Woodchuck, 1911; 33; 16117; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Deer, 1911; 34; 16118; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Larkspur, 1911; 35; 16120; 261; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Fringed Gentian, 1911; 36; 16121; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Camping outfit at Yellowstone, 1911; 37; 16122; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Camping outfit, 1911; 38; 16123; 195; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Campers, 1911; 39; 16124; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Madison River or Swan Lake Basin, 1911; 40; 16125; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Along the Madison River, 1911; 41; 16126; 156; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - The Madison River, 1911; 42; 16127; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Junction of the Firehole and Gibbon Rivers, 1911; 43; 16128; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Gibbon Falls, 1911; 44; 16129; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Gibbon Falls (80 feet), 1911; 45; 16130; 253; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Chocolate Spring, 1911; 46; 16131; 232; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Chocolate Springs near Norris, 1911; 47; 16132; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Boiling pool, 1911; 48; 16133; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Road and geyser, Norris, 1911; 49; 16134; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Road to Norris, 1911; 50; 16135; 194; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Norris Hotel, 1911; 51; 16136; 158; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Norris Geyser Basin, general view, 1911; 52; 16137; 160; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Paint Pot in Norris Basin, 1911; 53; 16138; 166; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - Second Paint Pot in Norris Basin, 1911; 54; 16139; 163; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  - The Bathtub, Norris Basin, 1911; 55; 16140; 226; 4x5 (Box 1253)
  Box 1254
- Yellowstone National Park, 2.1.1.1.31
  - Mud Geyser, Norris Basin, 1911; 1; 16141; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Mud Geyser, Norris Basin, 1911; 2; 16142; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Mud Geyser, Norris Basin, 1911; 3; 16143; 162; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Coaches, 1911; 4; 16144; 329; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Stages, 1911; 5; 16145; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Along the Gardiner River, 1911; 6; 16146; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Swan Lake Basin, 1911; 7; 16147; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Road through forest, 1911; 8; 16148; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Side of Roaring Mountain, 1911; 9; 16149; 256; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Obsidian Cliff, 1911; 10; 16150; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Electric Peak, 1911; 11; 16151; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Coach on the road near the Golden Gate, 1911; 12; 16152; 161; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Hoodoos, 1911; 13; 16153; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Hoodoos, 1911; 14; 16154; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The White Elephant, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 15; 16155; 181; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Angel Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 16; 16156; 229; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Part of Angel Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 17; 16157; 257; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Liberty Cap, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 18; 16158; 255; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Liberty Cap and Hymen Terrace, 1911; 19; 16159; 254; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Devil’s Thumb, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 20; 16160; 164; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party at cone of the Great Geyser, 1911; 21; 16162; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Miss Heyder near Angel Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, 1911; 22; 16163; 200; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Inspiration Point, Grand Canyon of Yellowstone, 1911; 23; 16164; 186; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Mammoth Paint Pots, Lower Basin, 1911; 24; 16165; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Approaching the Upper Basin, 1911; 25; 16166; 154; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Along the Firehole River, 1911; 26; 16167; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Along the Firehole River, 1911; 27; 16168; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Riverside Geyser, Upper Basin, 1911; 28; 16169; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Hot pool with wildflowers, Upper Basin, 1911; 29; 16170; 224; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Geysers along the Firehole River, Upper Basin, 1911; 30; 16171; 332; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Frank R. Roberson at the Fan Geyser, Upper Basin, 1911; 31; 16172; 153; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party at the Punch Bowl, Upper Basin, 1911; 32; 16173; 327; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Looking into heart of hot spring, 1911; 33; 16174; 334; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Frank R. Roberson at hot pool, Upper Basin, 1911; 34; 16175; 330; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Economic Geyser, Upper Basin, 1911; 35; 16176; 225; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Crater of the Great Geyser, 1911; 36; 16177; 246; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Color effect near Biscuit Basin, 1911; 37; 16178; 243; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Cone of the Giant Geyser, Upper Basin, 1911; 38; 16179; 331; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Morning Glory Spring, Upper Basin, 1911; 39; 16180; 157; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Frank R. Roberson at Castle Geyser, Upper Basin, 1911; 40; 16181; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Castle Geyser cone, Upper Basin, 1911; 41; 16182; 237; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Grotto Geyser in action, Upper Basin, 1911; 42; 16183; 242; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Giantess in eruption, 1911; 43; 16184; 228; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Side of Old Faithful crater, 1911; 44; 16185; 165; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Looking into crater of Old Faithful, 1911; 45; 16186; 172; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Frank R. Roberson on the crater of Old Faithful, 1911; 46; 16187; 171; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Snow in June, Old Faithful Inn, 1911; 47; 16188; 333; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The cone of the Lone Star Geyser, 1911; 48; 16189; 170; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Lone Star Geyser cone, 1911; 49; 16190; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Lone Star Geyser in action, 1911; 50; 16191; 238; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Lone Star Geyser, 1911; 51; 16192; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Lone Star Geyser in action, 1911; 52; 16193; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Continental Divide and Isa Lake, 1911; 53; 16194; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Continental Divide in June, 1911; 54; 16195; 176; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Bad roads, 1911; 55; 16196; 230; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Frank R. Roberson and bad road, 1911; 56; 16197; 215; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Yellowstone Lake near the Thumb, 1911; 57; 16198; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The Fishing Cone in Yellowstone Lake, near the Thumb, 1911; 58; 16199; 202; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Road near Thumb, 1911; 59; 16200; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Between the Thumb and Lake Hotel, 1911; 60; 16201; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Mud volcano, 1911; 61; 16202; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - The mud volcano, 1911; 62; 16203; 252; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Yellowstone Lake and mountains, 1911; 63; 16204; 251; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - People leaving the Lake Hotel, 1911; 64; 16205; 247; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  - Yellowstone Lake through the trees, 1911; 65; 16206; 248; 4x5 (Box 1254)
  Box 1255
- Yellowstone National Park, 2.1.1.1.31
  - Yellowstone River, 1911; 1; 16207; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Upper Falls, spray, 1911; 2; 16208; 191; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Upper Falls, 1911; 3; 16209; 231; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Yellowstone River near the big bridge, 1911; 4; 16210; 190; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Grand Canyon Bridge, 1911; 5; 16211; 258; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Canyon and Yellowstone River, 1911; 6; 16212; 185; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Grand Canyon and Yellowstone River, showing colored rocks, 1911; 7; 16213; 183; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Frank R. Roberson at Inspiration Point, canyon, 1911; 8; 16214; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Colored rock in Grand Canyon, 1911; 9; 16215; 189; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - On the brink of the canyon, 1911; 10; 16216; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Frank R. Roberson and woman at Glacial Boulder, Grand Canyon, 1911; 11; 16217; 184; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - Between Norris and the canyon, 1911; 12; 16218; 4x5 (Box 1255)
  - The White Dome near Great Fountain Geyser, 1911; 13; 16219; 4x5 (Box 1255)